[
  {
    "id": "Q7jjKo",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "I can say ... for example",
    "back": "mogę powiedzieć ... na przykład",
    "pronunciation": "MOH-geh NAHP-SHIH-qwahd"
  },
  {
    "id": "mQQL8A",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "how can I say ... in Polish",
    "back": "jak powiedzieć ... po polsku",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "IQTpNs",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "that's great",
    "back": "to świetnie",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "PTPkqa",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "I want to speak more polish",
    "back": "chcę mówić bardziej po polsku",
    "pronunciation": "hitSEH...BAR-jay"
  },
  {
    "id": "dCHzoB",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "but it is difficult",
    "back": "ale to trudne",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "yXpTPw",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "yes, I speak a little Polish",
    "back": "tak, mówię trochę po polsku",
    "pronunciation": "MOO-vee-yeh TROH-/ch/ay"
  },
  {
    "id": "EPTyvp",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "numbers 1-20",
    "back": "jeden, dwa, trzy, cztery, pięć, sześć, siedem, osiem, dziewięć, dziesięć, jedenaście, dwanaście, trzynaście, czternaście, piętnaście, szesnaście, siedemnaście, osiemnaście, dziewiętnaście, dwadzieścia.",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "oPJtRX",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "numbers 20, 30, ... 100",
    "back": "dwadzieścia, trzydzieści, czterdzieści, pięćdziesiąt, sześćdziesiąt, siedemdziesiąt, osiemdziesiąt, dziewięćdziesiąt, sto",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "TNbBCB",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "our application will crash",
    "back": "notre application va planter",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bJFm7V",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "the hosting plan",
    "back": "le plan d'hébergement",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ggEp0G",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "the intended meaning",
    "back": "la signification voulue",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9zTHRm",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "to implement",
    "back": "mettre en oeuvre",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "W40Kp7",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "cloud provider",
    "back": "fournisseur de cloud",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "qHIq5e",
    "category": "es",
    "front": "click the button",
    "back": "haz clic en el botón",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cUgFcX",
    "category": "es",
    "front": "screen recording",
    "back": "grabación de pantalla",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "slwPiu",
    "category": "es",
    "front": "ultimately",
    "back": "por último",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2WT5Yp",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "I was hungry",
    "back": "Byłem głodny",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dASdz3",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "Where were you?",
    "back": "Gdzie byłeś?",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "veG3ct",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "Were you there?",
    "back": "Byłeś tam?",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "OldGZF",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "Were you at home yesterday?",
    "back": "Byłeś wczoraj w domu?",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "zP9Sgh",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "Where are we?",
    "back": "Gdzie jesteśmy?",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "hmhllz",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "We're creative.",
    "back": "Jesteśmy kreatywni.",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "Ov0ozu",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "We're ready.",
    "back": "Jesteśmy gotowi.",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "MdbiXQ",
    "category": "linux",
    "front": "what commands do you have to run before you install software with `apt-get`",
    "back": "`sudo apt-get update` and `sudo apt-get upgrade`",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ZBefYN",
    "category": "pl",
    "front": "I want to learn more Polish.",
    "back": "Chcę nauczyć się więcej języka polskiego.",
    "pronunciation": "tSEH sheh vee-EN-SAY YEHsika"
  },
  {
    "id": "XSC2r0",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "quote: everything has already been said, but since no one listens, we always have to start again",
    "back": "\"Toutes chose sont dites déjà, mais comme personne n'écoute, il faut toujours recommencer.\" - André Gide",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "NPiWsT",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "as fast as him",
    "back": "aussi vite que lui",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0KfvwU",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "a small success",
    "back": "un petit succès",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "Z3LefY",
    "category": "fr",
    "front": "the house",
    "back": "la maison",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "vIyTSj",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "What is that called?",
    "back": "Hvad hedder det?",
    "pronunciation": "veLL hiTHa TEE"
  },
  {
    "id": "vjWVnS",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Hello, my name is Edward",
    "back": "Goddag, jeg hedder Edward",
    "pronunciation": "goo-DAY JIGH-hiTHa Edward"
  },
  {
    "id": "dHb16B",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "No, I am from America, but I live in Berlin.",
    "back": "Nej, jeg er fra America, men jeg bor i Berlin.",
    "pronunciation": "NIGH, jai eh fra America, men jigh BOR ee Berlin"
  },
  {
    "id": "hoX83B",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Good evening, Sara.",
    "back": "God aften, Sara.",
    "pronunciation": "go-AFFdn"
  },
  {
    "id": "Uy0GNx",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "I'm learning Danish.",
    "back": "jeg laerer dansk.",
    "pronunciation": "jai lehrer densk"
  },
  {
    "id": "fJthfx",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "It is easy to read and write Danish, but it is hard to pronounce Danish correctly.",
    "back": "Det er let at laese og skrive dansk, men det er svaert at udtale dansk korrekt.",
    "pronunciation": "day er lit o layze o skreeva densk, meh day er svairt o oo-TAY-leh densk korrekt"
  },
  {
    "id": "bJnx7Z",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Hi Sara, how are you doing? / Good, thanks.",
    "back": "Dav Sara, hvordan har du det? / Fint, tak.",
    "pronunciation": "dah-ow sara, vah-denn HAH doo day"
  },
  {
    "id": "ukhTcr",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Two beers, please.",
    "back": "To øl, tak.",
    "pronunciation": "toh öl tahk"
  },
  {
    "id": "gQj8AA",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "I don't understand.",
    "back": "Undskyld., jeg forstår det ikke.",
    "pronunciation": "OON-skool, ya foh-stow DAY eeg"
  },
  {
    "id": "vnGFq5",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "I am a smart guy.",
    "back": "Jeg er en smart fyr.",
    "pronunciation": "yay er ain smart für"
  },
  {
    "id": "suCsyL",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Good morning, Sara.",
    "back": "God morgen, Sara.",
    "pronunciation": "go mourn, Sara"
  },
  {
    "id": "UDq0JD",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "I'm doing fine, thank you.",
    "back": "Jeg har det godt, tak.",
    "pronunciation": "YIGH har de GAWD, tahk."
  },
  {
    "id": "K6NOdt",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Wonderful",
    "back": "Glimrende",
    "pronunciation": "GLEEM-en-nah"
  },
  {
    "id": "Sq8KsR",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Auf wiedersehen",
    "back": "Farvel",
    "pronunciation": "far-VELL"
  },
  {
    "id": "JMWFjk",
    "category": "denmark",
    "front": "name the 10 largest islands",
    "back": "1. Zealand (Sjælland [zay-LENN]), 2. Vendsyssel-Thy [VENN-sissell-TSEE], 3. Funen (Fyn [feen]), 4. Lolland [loll-LEN], 5. Bornholm [bon-HOLM], 6. Falster [FEL-stah], 7. Langeland [LONG-eh-lan], 8. Mors [mors], 9. Als [els], 10. Amager [ah-mah]@@largestIslands",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "eHbZqY",
    "category": "denmark",
    "front": "name largest islands 11-20",
    "back": "1. Møn [mün], 2. Læsø [LESS-ü], 3. Samsø [SAM-sü], 4. Rømø [RÜ-mü], 5. Fanø [FAYN-ü], 6. Tåsinge [TOH-sing-eh], 7. Ærø [AY-rö], 8. Fur [FOO-ah], 9. Anholt [en-HOLT], 10. Saltholm [selt-HOLM]@@islands11to20",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "XN2b1y",
    "category": "denmark",
    "front": "name the 10 largest cities",
    "back": "1. København [KÖ-pen-HAU-en], 2. Århus [OH-hoos], 3. Odense [OH-in-zah], 4. Ålborg [all-BOH], 5. Esbjerg [es-bee-YA], 6. Randers [rah-nahs], 7. Kolding [koh-ling], 8. Horsens [HOH-sins], 9. Vejle [VIGH-leh], 10. Roskilde [RUSS-kee-leh]@@cities1to10",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "25gSip",
    "category": "denmark",
    "front": "name the 11th-20th largest cities",
    "back": "1. Herning [HAIR-ning], 2. Silkeborg [SIL-kah-boh], 3. Fredericia [FREH-rish-sha], 4. Viborg [vee-boh], 5. Køge [kü], 6. Holstebro [HOL-sti-bro], 7. Slagelse [SLAY-ill-za], 8. Holbæk [HOL-bek], 9. Sønderborg [SÖ-na-boh], 10. Svendborg [SVIN-boh]@@cities11to20",
    "pronunciation": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dvvZjS",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "What's this flower called?",
    "back": "Hvad hedder denne blomst?",
    "pronunciation": "VEH hethah dain blomst"
  },
  {
    "id": "jDGe6T",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Denmark hedder Danmark på dansk.",
    "back": "Denmark is called Danmark in Danish.",
    "pronunciation": "pah densk"
  },
  {
    "id": "3EEFdb",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Ved du hvad han hedder?",
    "back": "Do you know his name?",
    "pronunciation": "vill DOO vah hen HILLah"
  },
  {
    "id": "v32WoA",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Ved du hvad hun hedder?",
    "back": "Do you know her name?",
    "pronunciation": "vill DOO vah hoon HILLah"
  },
  {
    "id": "GoqmA6",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Undskyld, noget er gået galt.",
    "back": "Sorry, something has gone wrong.",
    "pronunciation": "OON-skool, noah air GO-ah gayt"
  },
  {
    "id": "a9vTx8",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Undskyld mig, hvor er udgangen?",
    "back": "Excuse me, where is the exit?",
    "pronunciation": "OON-skool migh, voh air OO-gan(k)-/en/"
  },
  {
    "id": "WjJwtE",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Undskyld mig, må jeg åbne vinduet?",
    "back": "Excuse me, may I open the window?",
    "pronunciation": "OON-skool migh, moh ya ohpne VIN-doo-ah"
  },
  {
    "id": "4NfDIh",
    "category": "da",
    "front": "Godt spørgsmål.",
    "back": "Good question.",
    "pronunciation": "got spös-MOHl"
  }
]